wipmania.com 2012-10-24

# WIPmania - WorldIP free geolocation database, service and tools - Datenschutzerklärung

Last modified on 31. January 2011

**Privacy Policy**

We also have the right to revise or change the Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. We are the sole and final arbiter as the interpretation of these rules. Any use of the WIPmania.com after the effective date of such modifications will be deemed as acceptance of these changes by the User of our Website.

**Security**

The security of sensitive, financial information is important to us. We take technical and physical steps to protect sensitive, financial information that you provide to us. In addition, this Website uses industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to transmit all sensitive information between your web browser and our server. All local storage of personal information is safe guarded with our best effort.

The information that you send through this Website, including e-mail messages, will not be encrypted unless we advise you otherwise. Although our Website has industry standard security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of the information that is under our control, we cannot guarantee complete security.

**Your Personal Information**

We respect and protect your privacy. Your information is kept strictly confidential and would be only disclosed as required by law. We may ask for personal data such as your name and/or e-mail address when you use our Website. We collect basic personal information when you fill out the contact forms or subscribe to our newsletter.  
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Website, used to notify visitors about updates to our Website, and also for marketing purposes and to contact you when necessary.  
You do not have to provide any personal information on our Website unless you choose to do so.

It will also not be published anywhere, except your Nick/Name in the comments to articles on OpenBlog.

**IP-address**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends when you visit our website. We use also IP addresses to correct the Database. Certain sections of this site log and display your IP-address. IP-addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and are not secret, many of the websites will record and display IP-addresses. We use IP-addresses to analyze trends and statistics, administer the site and improve our Website for aggregate use.

**Your E-Mail**

For each visitor to our Website, our Web server automatically recognizes only the User's domain name, but not the e-mail address.  
Your e-mail we collect only by your registration, it is your entries in the system and our possibility to have a contact with you. If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each e-mail.  
We will not sell, transmit, share or disclose it to any third parties.  
We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, through our Website.

**Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard drive which identify you when you enter a particular websites. We use session cookies to determine your browser. This information does not identify you personally, but provides you with data, such as the identified number. Cookies allow us to analyze and improve the usefulness of the information at our Websites.  
It can be also turned off independently. A rejection of cookies may lead to functions and services will not work properly.

**Links to Other Sites**

We may provide hyperlinks to other websites or resources that are not owned or controlled by us. We cannot be responsible for the content on other websites, privacy and security, any products or services on these sites. We also cannot guarantee the completeness, accuracy, relevance and timeliness of the information or the resources contained on these or any other websites.  
We are also not responsible for any loss and damages that may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of use of any advertising on these sites.

We welcome your comments or questions about our Websites. If you have any questions or comments regarding this document, please contact us via e-mail at mail @ wipmania.com.
